# **AGILE MATHEW**

Mobile No : +918129688393

Code Repository : <a href="https://github.com/AgileMathew">https://github.com/AgileMathew</a>

Email: agilemathew@gmail.com

Moonnumackal House Kadanad P O Kottayam Dist

## **SUMMARY**

Seeking a challenging and rewarding opportunity as Software QA Engineer/ApplicationTester with an organization that recognizes and utilizes my potential and analytical & technical skills.

Having 8 months experience as manual tester and 2 years of experience as Python/Odoo Developer. Relevant experience in developing Odoo/OpenERP modules for Sales, Purchase, Human Resources, Manufacturing, Accounting etc. Passionate to work in OpenSource Technologies.

## PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Date of Birth : 9th May 1991

Nationality : Indian
Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Permanent : Kerala, India

Residence

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

# **Bachelor's Degree (B-Tech)**

Field of Study : Information Technology and Engineering

Institute/Universit : Govt. Engg. College, Sreekrishnapuram, Palakkad, Kerala

y : 2009-2013

Year

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

**Company :- Eram Infotech** 

Position Title: Software

Engineer

Year: Dec 2017 - Present

**Company:- BroadTech Solutions** 

Position Title: Program

Analyst

Year: Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

**Company:- Recursive Tech** 

Position Title: Software Developer

Year: Oct 2015 - Aug 2016

## **PROJECTS**

Derive: Derive is a Travel Accounting System(TAS) is a complete solution for

Mid and Back Office ERP developed using Odoo 10.0. The TAS is simple, secure and do more with less manpower. Worked as application tester for the application.

Worked for automation testing for parsing files in various extensions using python code for Automation testing in selenium and load testing using jmeter.

**Cheshhtasya**: User Access Control, Daily Expense Report, Stock Daily Tracker, Products uom change according to list.

**Gastro**: Hotel Bookings, Report Changes (Qweb), Functionality Changes.

**PaperShow**: Event Management, Report Changes (Rml), Imported CSV files to the project.

Rental Management: Custormized Module for rental vehicle

**Promgifts**: Report Changes

- Worked in Odoo 10,9,8,7,6 versions
- Odoo Module Development using Python.
- Database Administration PostgreSQL
- Reporting tools : RML, Jasper, Qweb
- Testing in web applications
- Setup jmeter for load testing

## **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that all information given above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.